UI Bug List

#1) When the list of items is greater than 8, then you 
can’t scroll because of the overflow-y: hidden. 
- Quick Fix? Simple if statement for when there is 8 
	or more then set the overflow-y to normal? Setting the 
	home screens display to none so that way you can’t 
	scroll up.
- Issue with this, 
	would have to set a display: block,  
	when clicking the nav to fix this issue. as well as having 
	the debt area being set to none initially to not one able 
	to scroll over it.
Fixed? :: Yes, Just need to add the change when I add the nav with the new page .